(Howard:)Space is beautiful, Earth is beautiful.
Same old, same old.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Everything's fine, heh.
- Howard.
(Howard:)The other astronauts
are being mean to me.
(Bernadette:)No, what are they doing?
(Howard:)Well, like, for instance,
the other day, when I was asleep...
(Howard:)...one of the guys
went on a space-walk...
(Howard:)...and glued a big-eyed rubber alien mask
to the outside of my window.
(Howard:)When I woke up,
I screamed for like nine minutes.
(Bernadette:)Oh, Howie.
(Howard:)You can see it if you want.
It's on YouTube.
Google "Astronaut screams
for nine minutes."
(Bernadette:)Why don't you stand up to them?
(Howard:)What am I supposed to say?
(Penny:)I don't know.
Say, "Being mean is lame.
What's cool is being nice."